Las Vegas Serial Killer is a horror, thriller film
directed by Ray Dennis Steckler.
August 31, 1986: Dangerously unhinged serial killer Johnathan Glick gets
released from the Nevada State Penitentiary on a technicality.
Three days after his release Johnathan arrives in Las Vegas, Nevada.
Naturally, Johnathan decides to embark on another murderous rampage
that came to be known as "The Glitter Gulch Holocaust".
Clarence, played by Ron Jason.
Jonathan Klick, played by Pierre Agostino.
Kat Carson, played by Kathryn Downey.
Jack, played by Chris Cave.
Miss World Burlesque, played by Toni Alessandrini.
Photographer's Model, played by Suzee Slater.
This is a list of notable serial killers, by the
country where most of the killings occurred.
The tone is dark and intense.